Guide to the Time Inc. Travel Services Records 1989-1995 MS 3009-RG 52
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Travel Services Records
1989-1995
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 52
2 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
Time Inc. Travel Services arranged business travel for Time Inc. employees. The collection comes from the files of Tom McDermott, Travel Services Director in 1995.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are stored offsite and advance notice is required for use. Please contact manuscripts@nyhistory.org prior to your research visit to coordinate access. Keep in mind that it will take between two (2) and five (5) business days for collections to arrive, and you should plan your research accordingly.
Open to qualified researchers with the exception of restricted materials. Restricted materials include contracts. Restricted materials are located in box R86.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically based on the original arrangement.
Provenance
Gift of Time Inc. in 2015.
Related Materials
This finding aid relates to just one record group of the Time Inc. Records. For information about the other record groups and for overall information about the archives, please see the Guide to the Time Inc. Records (MS 3009). The Henry Luce Papers (MS 3014) were acquired with the Time Inc. Records. The collection of books acquired with the records are cataloged as the Time Inc. Reference Library. Additional material on Travel Services can be found in the Time Inc. Reference Files (MS-3009-RG 3) and the Time Inc. Annex Files (MS-3009-RG 39.
Scope and Contents
Time Inc. Travel Services arranged business travel for Time Inc. employees. The collection consists of the files of Tom McDermott, Travel Services Director in 1995, and contains correspondence, information on airlines and accommodation for travelers, invoices, budgets, performance reviews, and plans for specific large-scale group travel for Time Inc. employees.
Corporation records; Corporations -- History; Corporations -- New York (State); Publishers and publishing -- New York (State) -- New York.; Organization files; Time, inc. -- Archives; Time, inc. -- History
- Actual Costs vs. Budgets, 1995 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 1)
- American Trans Air (ATA)/Starflite, 1995 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 2)
- Maritz Travel Company, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 3-4)
- Maritz Travel Company: Invoices, 1994-1995 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 5)
- Olympics Miscellany, 1992 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 6)
- Olympics, 1992 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 7)
- Olympics: Tom McDermott Binder, 1992 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 8)
- Sports Illustrated Olympic "Team" Manual, 1992 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 9)
- Third Party Expenses, 1995 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 10)
- Thomas Cook Travel: Revenue Share Analysis, 1994 (Offsite-box 4089, Folder 11)
- Time Newstour '95, 1995 (Offsite-box 4090, Folder 1-2)
- Time Newstour '95 [Restricted], 1995 (Offsite-box R86, Folder 92)
- Time Warner Inc. Corporate Conference, 1989 (Offsite-box 4090, Folder 3)
- Time Warner Inc. Corporate Conference Binder, 1989 (Offsite-box 4090, Folder 4-6)
- Time Warner Inc. Corporate Conference Binder [Restricted], 1989 (Offsite-box R86)
  Scope and Contents
  Includes digital material:
  1 computer discs (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in. On label: Lyford Cay Ground Arrivals and Departures – Please Note Different Files
  1 computer discs (floppy disk): 3 1/2 in. Unlabled.